09. Sophie Brittain
 

Graphic designer Sophie Brittain welcomes visitors to her site with a top fold that’s just as playful as it is minimal. With a white background and very little imagery, she allows a concise introductory sentence to take up the majority of the space.


Sophie’s unique use of microcopy is also evident in the website’s footer, as she opts for clever wording choices in place of icons for her social media links. She labels her Instagram account as 'Me, taking pictures,' and her email shows up under 'You, writing a fan letter.'
